{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500790424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500790423"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 92f64fff-39c7-4f96-9e6e-e2b228b20688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500793903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500793903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 92f64fff-39c7-4f96-9e6e-e2b228b20688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500799315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500799315"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 92f64fff-39c7-4f96-9e6e-e2b228b20688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500809621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500809621"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500810168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500810167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500811673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500811672"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500812591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500812590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500813326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500813326"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500813810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500813810"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500814616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500814615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500817680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500817680"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500817904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500817903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500818388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500818388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500819307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500819306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500821060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500821060"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500821832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500821832"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500822375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500822375"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500823779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500823779"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500824620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500824619"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500825191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500825190"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500828699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500828698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500830047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500830046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500831343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500831343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500833007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500833006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500835937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500835937"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500836765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500836764"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500837047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500837046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500838004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500838003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500839099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500839099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500839360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500839359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500842426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500842426"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500842678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500842677"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500843171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500843170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500843898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500843897"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500845312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500845312"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500847306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500847305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500848805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500848804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500850292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500850291"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500850478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500850477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500851616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500851616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500852640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500852639"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500852874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500852874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500853878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500853878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500856764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500856764"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500858509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500858509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500859844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500859843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500861318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500861318"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500862034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500862033"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500863560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500863559"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500864428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500864427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500866051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500866051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500867404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500867404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500870268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500870267"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500870499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500870498"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500870968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500870968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500871719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500871719"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500873476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500873476"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500874241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500874240"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500874895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500874894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500875661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500875660"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500876516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500876516"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500880055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500880055"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500880758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500880757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500881934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500881933"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500883398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500883398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500884044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500884044"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500887513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500887513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500888368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500888367"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500889531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500889531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500890988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500890987"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500891822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500891820"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500893756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500893756"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500896957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500896957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500898259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500898259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500899361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500899361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500900635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500900634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500901393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500901393"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500904442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500904442"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500906007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500906007"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500906927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500906926"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500907188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500907188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500908032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500908031"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500908174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500908174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500908866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500908866"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500910387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500910386"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500910717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500910716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500911441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500911439"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500915184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500915183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500916100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500916099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500916785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500916784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500917811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500917811"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500918618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500918617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500919380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500919380"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500920306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500920305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500921420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500921420"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500921887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500921886"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500922734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500922734"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500924097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500924096"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500924300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500924300"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500924806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500924806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500928366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500928366"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500929729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500929729"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500930393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500930392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500931977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500931977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500933273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500933272"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500934496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500934496"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500937133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500937132"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500937217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500937217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" 4c2ca70a-95ec-48ad-9c52-5be5fe5b252e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500949709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500949709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500950251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500950251"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500951744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500951744"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500952647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500952647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500953369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500953369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500953842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500953842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500954635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500954634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500957730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500957729"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500957953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500957953"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500958435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500958435"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500959349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500959349"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500961117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500961116"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500961891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500961891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500962433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500962433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500963848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500963847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500964685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500964685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500965248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500965247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500968701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500968700"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500970040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500970040"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500971323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500971322"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500972976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500972976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500975856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500975856"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500976678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500976678"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500976958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500976958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500977909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500977909"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500979016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500979015"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500979279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500979278"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500982261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500982260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500982513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500982513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500983002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500983001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500983726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500983725"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500985140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500985139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500987139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500987139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500988634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500988633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500990125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500990124"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500990300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500990300"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500991438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500991437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500992477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500992476"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500992725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500992724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500993741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500993741"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500996593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500996593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500998326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500998326"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548500999649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548500999649"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501001113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501001113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501001816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501001816"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501003329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501003329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501004182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501004182"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501005820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501005819"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501007174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501007174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501010084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501010083"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501010307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501010306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501010769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501010769"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501011514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501011513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501013263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501013262"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501014029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501014028"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501014688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501014688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501015456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501015455"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501016310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501016309"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501019814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501019814"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501020506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501020506"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501021670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501021670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501023133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501023133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501023772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501023772"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501027147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501027147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501028004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501028003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501029167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501029166"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501030609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501030609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501031422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501031422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501033355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501033355"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501036607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501036607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501037913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501037912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501039006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501039006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501040269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501040269"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501041012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501041011"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501043995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501043995"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501045558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501045558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501046464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501046464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501046717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501046717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501047562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501047561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501047696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501047696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501048391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501048391"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501049906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501049906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501050230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501050230"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501050947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501050946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501054659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501054658"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501055575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501055574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501056259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501056259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501057284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501057284"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501058091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501058090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501058844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501058844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501059757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501059757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501060860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501060860"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501061313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501061313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501062146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501062146"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501063505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501063503"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501063710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501063709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501064215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501064214"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501067825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501067824"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501069191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501069189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501069856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501069856"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501071430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501071430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501072713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501072713"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501073935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501073935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501076567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501076566"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501076650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501076650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501087451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501087451"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501134360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501134359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_140614"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}